Tell me about my biological father.
Now.
You and Jiang Yu went to great lengths
to bring me here
just to avenge Jiang Yuqing, didn't you?
Wen Jianan, you've got the wrong person.
Is what you saw and found out
really the truth?
Jiang Yuqing
is the only woman
I've ever truly loved in my life.
Why would I kill her?
I wanted her alive more than anyone else.
Even if she hates me,
it's better than living like a corpse
all these years.
He Mu.
Even now, you are still
pretending to be affectionate.
That's what they wanted you to hear.
I am afraid the truth
would break you.
You wouldn't be able to handle it.
The person you've always respected,
admired, and relied on
is the real devil in human skin.
What exactly are you trying to say?
It's Wen Yanhui.
He was the one who told me
to get close to Wen Xin and control her.
He also ordered me to get rid of
Jiang Yuqing, the unstable factor.
Because Jiang Yuqing knew too many
of the Wen family's dirty secrets.
And when I was hesitating,
he controlled me
by threatening what I feared losing most.
Wen Yanhui is the real murderer.
I'm nothing but a bloodstained knife
he is ready to discard
because it's gotten too dirty.
You hate him, so you want to
drag him down with you before you die.
Why should I believe
the crazy talk of a murderer?
I knew it.
Even if you knew the truth,
you wouldn't dare kill him,
because Wen Yanhui
is your biological father.
Your grandfather is actually
your real father.
Wen Jianan.
You are the bastard he had
with another woman.
Your entire Wen family are animals.
Animals.
Alright, put it down.
I'm telling you.
Put it down.
If you want to know everything,
go ask Wen Xin.
Wen Xin will tell you.
Put it down.
Go.
Animals.
[Dearest Episode 13]
[20 years ago]
Good. I wasn't wrong about you.
If you hadn't told me,
I never would have known
that the Cheng family's son
was trying to hook up with my daughter.
I've been
fighting with his father for years.
There is no way
I'm letting him marry my daughter.
Have her get an abortion.
You're abandoning me
to be with that woman.
You're just after the Wen family's money.
You're right.
I am after the Wen family's money.
I'm only with her
so I can take over the Wen family.
Yuqing.
I want you to have a better life.
That's why I'm with her.
However, I promise you,
you will have everything she has.
Yuqing.
I had no choice but to be with her.
You are the life I truly want.
I spent all my savings on this ring,
made from volcanic stone, just for you.
It's one of a kind in the world.
Once I take over the Wen family,
I will have you by my side,
openly and proudly,
as the rightful lady of the house.
Leave.
Don't come back.
This family doesn't need you.
Don't be too sad.
In the future,
we will also have
a child of our own.
Dad.
She was born from another woman
who got into my bed while I was drunk.
Since you lost your child,
just raise her as your own.
It was only later that I realized...
Chenghan's death back then
must have been allowed by Dad.
Otherwise, none of this
could have happened right under his nose.
Someone who shares my blood
killed the person I loved the most.
It's ridiculous.
Yeah.
I'm actually Wen Yanhui's child.
And you... are my sister.
I didn't know who my father was.
Now, I don't know who my mother is.
I lost my child back then.
Dad brought you back.
For a long time,
I treated you as my own child.
I projected all the love for that child
onto you.
But later I suddenly realized
that it was unfair to my dead child.
I'm sorry, Jianan,
for treating you so badly.
You're right.
I am pathetic.
The only person who truly loved me
was murdered.
And I married the murderer.
My father made me raise his child
to cover up the scandal
of his illegitimate child.
Jianan, you wouldn't understand.
You're a shining superstar.
Everyone likes you.
And I...
I just keep rotting away, day by day.
This isn't over.
There are still many answers
waiting to come to light.
Some people still
haven't paid the price yet.
When your child was killed back then,
Wen Yanhui allowed it to happen.
So when He Mu framed me,
it's highly likely he knew about it too.
But he still chose to turn a blind eye.
Because this way,
he could kill two birds with one stone.
With one life,
he could control both me and He Mu.
If he really is the one
who turned all our lives and destinies
upside down
while sitting back
and reaping the benefits,
I won't sit by and do nothing anymore.
I promised Jiang Yu
that everyone who hurt us
would pay the price.
Wen Xin,
are you really willing to just let it go?
But what can I possibly do against him?
What else can I do?
Everyone has weaknesses.
Wen Yanhui must have one too.
You know him better than I do.
I need you to tell me
what he fears most
and what he's most desperate to hide.
How could he have weaknesses?
He has always been the authority.
He is unquestionable.
Whatever he does is right.
Even the whole Wen...
What is it?
He has a weakness.
There is someone.
Her death was very sudden,
and suspicious.
Who?
Wen Yan.
My mother,